Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - Bamu content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/741 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR801)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Torobina village. Songs 4-8. Collected by Todd and Mary Saurman. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Bamu content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/742 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR802)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Torobina village. Songs 9-17. Collected by Todd and Mary Saurman. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Bamu content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/743 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR803)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Bunigi village. Songs 18-22. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Vida Chenoweth talk, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/743.1 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR804)
    Contents: An Evening with Vida Chenoweth, Barrows Auditorium. Produced by Patricia Swindle.
  - Bamu content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/744 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR805)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Torobina village. Songs 23-33. Collected by Todd and Mary Saurman. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Bamu content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/745 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR806)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Torobina village. Songs 46-48. Collected by Todd and Mary Saurman. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Bamu content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/746 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR807)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Torobina village. Songs 63-68. Collected by Todd and Mary Saurman. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Bamu men and women's songs, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/747 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR808)
    Papua New Guinea. Western Province. Contents: Torobina village. Songs 72-79. Men and women's songs. Collected by Todd and Mary Saurman. People/language group: Bamu language.
  - Sio content, ca. 1991, 1 sound cassette; C91/748 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR809)
    Papua New Guinea. Morobe Province. Contents: Lambutina Village. Dr. Chenoweth-Supervisor. Collected by Shawn Dey, Mary and Todd Saurman. People/language group: Sio.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1988, 1 sound cassette; C88/750 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR811)
  - Wheaton College student songs, 1991-12, 1 sound cassette; C91/751 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR812)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R68/753 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR814)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R67/754 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR815)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R60/757 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR818)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R63/762 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR823)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R65/763b (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR824)
  - Sing-Sing for the birds, undated, 1 sound cassette; C91/769 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR830)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R61/771 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR832)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R62/772 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR833)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R63/773 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR834)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1992, 1 sound cassette; C92/780 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR841)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1992, 1 sound cassette; C92/780a (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR842)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1992, 1 sound cassette; C92/781 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR843)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1992, 1 sound cassette; C92/782 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR844)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1992, 1 sound cassette; C92/783 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR845)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1992, 1 sound cassette; C92/784 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR846)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/785 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR847)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/786 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR848)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/787 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR849)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/788 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR850)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/789 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR851)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/790 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR852)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1978, 1 sound cassette; C78/791 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR853)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1984, 1 sound cassette; C84/792 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR854)
  - Children's songs, ca. 1990, 1 sound cassette; C90/793 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR855)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1984, 1 sound cassette; C84/794 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR856)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1993, 1 sound cassette; C93/795 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR857)
  - Unidentified content, C94/797 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR859)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1994 ca. 1994, 1 sound cassette; C94/798 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR860)
  - Tanna Island songs, ca. 1994, 1 sound cassette; C94/799 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR861)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1994, 1 sound cassette; C94/800 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR862)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1995, 1 sound cassette; C95/801 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR863)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1995, 1 sound cassette; C95/802 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR864)
  - Yawu content, ca. 1995, 1 sound cassette; C95/803 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR865)
    Papua New Guinea. East Sepik Province. Bur village. Collected by Helen Marte. People/language group: Yawu language.
  - Banks Islands men's dances, 1994, 1 sound cassette; C94/804 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR866)
    Vanuatu. Banks Islands, Mota. Contents: Mariu village. Men's Dances. Collected by Dan Garst.
  - Custom music, Toka-Tolea, 1988, 1 sound cassette; C85/805 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR867)
    Contents: Custom Music Cont. (short time). Toka-Tolea.
  - Toka-Tolea music, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/806 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR868)
    Contents: Toka-Tolea (short time). Nasquash (Toka). Collected by Ruth Gordon.
  - Lamakaun music, 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/807 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR869)
    Contents: Lamakaun Music RG5, JB6. Custom Music. JB7 Burning Nasb song 001. Circumcision songs 053.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/808 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR870)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1981, 1 sound cassette; C81/809 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR871)
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette; C84/810 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR872)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1993, ca. 1984, 1 sound cassette; C93/811 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR873)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1993, 1 sound cassette; C93/812 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR874)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1993, 1 sound cassette; C93/813 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR875)
  - Women's fellowship, ca. 1996, 1 sound cassette; C96/814 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR876)
  - Cook Islands content, ca. 1996, 1 sound cassette; C96/815 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR877)
    Cook Islands. Rarotonga, Muri Beach.
  - Cook Islands content, ca. 1996, 1 sound cassette; C96/816 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR878)
    Cook Islands. Rarotonga. Ura Sarich's house. Various song categories sung.
  - Imene Tuki songs, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette; C97/817 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR879)
    Contents: Cook Islands Recording Project. CIPC Singers. Newton, Auckland, N.Z. Imene Tuki Songs 1-20.
  - Imene Tuki songs, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette; C97/818 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR880)
    Contents: Cook Islands Recording Project. CIPC Singers. Newton, Auckland, N.Z. Imene Tuki Songs 21-40.
  - Imene Tuki songs, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette; C97/818 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR881)
    Contents: Cook Islands Recording Project. CIPC Singers. Newton, Auckland, N.Z. Imene Tuki Songs 20-40.
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette; C97/819, C97/820A (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR882)
    Contents: Cook Islands Recording Project. Takamoa Theological College, Rarotonga. Panama Church, Nikao. Imene Tuki Songs 1-8.
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette; C97/820B, C97/821 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR883)
    Contents: Cook Islands Recording Project. Panama Church, Nikao, Rarotonga. Imene Tuki Songs 1-5, 7-10. Matavera Church, Rarotonga.
  - Cook Islands Recording Project, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette; C97/822 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR884)
    Contents: Cook Islands Recording Project. Ngatangiia Church, Rarotonga. Imene Tuki Songs 1-21.
  - Oro Province songs and dances, ca. 1967, 1 sound cassette; C67/823 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR885)
    Papua New Guinea. Oro Province. Contents: Baberade Village. 18 songs and dances by 40 women. Collected by Ziska Schwimmer.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1967, 1 sound tape reel; C67/824d (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR886)
  - Morobe Province content, undated (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR888)
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR889)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR891)
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR892)
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR893)
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR894)
  - Eastern Highlands, Kaagu girls songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR895)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Contents: Kaagu girls songs. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR896)
  - Eastern Highlands content, Araabutaa's songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel; Tape 2-4 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR897)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Neighbor sings Araabutaa's songs. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Eastern Highlands content, Araabutaa's songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel; Tape 2-5 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR898)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Kaarite. Araabutaa's songs. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Eastern Highlands content, Pomeko's songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel; Tape 2-6 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR899)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Pomeko's songs. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Eastern Highlands content, Pomeko's songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel; Tape 2-7 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR900)
  - Eastern Highlands content, Pomeko's songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel; Tape 2-8 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR901)
  - Eastern Highlands songs, undated, 1 sound tape reel; Tape 2-9 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR902)
    Papua New Guinea. Eastern Highlands Province. Contents: Kaarite Aitora songs. Song by Puqaa. Songs by Tonaaqe. People/language group: Usarufa.
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR903)
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR904)
  - Eastern Highlands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR905)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #01 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR906)
    Solomon Islands.
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #02 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR907)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #04 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR908)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #14 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR909)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #17 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR910)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #20 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR911)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #20/22 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR912)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #21 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR913)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #22 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR914)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #23 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR915)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #25 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR916)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #25 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR917)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #26A (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR918)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #26A (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR919)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #26A (cont.); #26B (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR920)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #33/27 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR921)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #29A, 33/27 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR922)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #29A (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR923)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #29B (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR924)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #29B (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR925)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #29C (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR926)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #30 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR927)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound cassette; #30; 31- 32 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR928)
  - Solomon Islands content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; #31/32 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR929)
  - New Zealand content, 1970, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR930)
    Auckland, New Zealand. Darlene Bee. SIL.
  - An Arapho Legacy, 2004-06-25, 1 sound disc (CDR) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR931)
    Contents: John Whiteshirt: An Arapaho Legacy.
  - An Arapho Legacy, 2004-06-25, 1 sound discs (CDR) (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR932)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R69/056 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR933)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1969, 1 sound tape reel; SR69/135 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR934)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R60/278 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR935)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel; R60/278 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR936)
  - Unidentified content, undated, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR937)
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR938)
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR939)
    Tape 2. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR940)
    Tape 3. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR941)
    Tape 4. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR942)
    Tape 5. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR943)
    Tape 6. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR944)
    Tape 8. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR945)
    Tape 9. Papua New Guinea, Pt. Moresby. S. Pacific Festival of Arts, Pt. Moresby.
  - Wewak Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette, C90 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR946)
    Papua New Guinea, Wewak. Tape 1.
  - Wewak Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR947)
  - Wewak Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR948)
    Papua New Guinea, Wewak. Tape 2.
  - Wewak Festival of Arts, 1980-07, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR949)
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR950)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 1.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR951)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 2.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR952)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 3.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR953)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 4.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR954)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 5.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR955)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 6.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR956)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 8.
  - S. Pacific Festival of Arts, 1980, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR957)
    Papua New Guinea. Tape 9.
  - Music Analysis Test, 1983-06-08, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR958)
    Papua New Guinea, Morobe Province. Music Analysis Test, Komba language.
  - Orya music, 1990-11-05, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR959)
    Indonesia, Irian Jaya. ORYA, Emic interval check of Orya music.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR960)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 1.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR961)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 2.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR962)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 20.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR963)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 25.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR964)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 26A.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR965)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 29B.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR966)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 30.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR967)
    Solomon Islands. Cassette 33/27.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR968)
    Solomon Islands. Reel 33/27.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR969)
    Solomon Islands. Reel 31/32.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR970)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #17.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR971)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #14.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR972)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #4.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR973)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #20.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR974)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #21.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR975)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #22.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR976)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #23.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR977)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #25.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR978)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #26A.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR979)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #26B. Track 1 only. Continuation of track 2 of original.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR980)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #29A. Track 1 of original.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR981)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #29B. Track 1: continuation of #29 original track 1 plus 5 minutes of track 2. Track 2: track 2 of original #29 cont'd.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR982)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #29C. Continuation of #29. Track 2 is blank.
  - Unidentified content, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR983)
    Solomon Islands. Reel #30.
  - Tape for analysis of Usarufa song styles, 1968-07, 1 sound tape reel (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR984)
    Papua New Guinea. Song list in sound recording documentation.
  - Darlene Bee lecture, 1970, 1 sound cassette (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR985)
    Auckland, New Zealand. Darlene Bee lectures on parallel meaning conveyed by speech and music, from notes by Vida Chenoweth.
- Series III: Graphic Images
  Note: Some digital files exist for still images that correspond to LOC 18 and LOC 36. LOC 18: Usarufa, Kaarite village, Papua New Guinea. LOC 36: Sursurunga, N. Ireland, Papua New Guinea.
  - Photographs from LOC 1, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 31/1)
    Darlene Bee and Vida Chenoweth with Usarufa people. Papua New Guinea, Eastern Highlands Province.
  - Photographs from LOC 6, 1966 (Box-folder 31/2)
    Warrior's tail. Papua New Guinea, Eastern Highlands Province.
  - Photographs from LOC 18 (folder 1 of 4), 1965 (Box-folder 31/3)
    Departure of Vida Chenoweth for the territory of New Guinea.
  - Photographs from LOC 18 (folder 2 of 4), 1958-1959 (Box-folder 31/4)
    Darlene Bee's photos at Kaagu, etc.
  - Photographs from LOC 18 (folder 3 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 31/5)
    Usarufa women.
  - Photographs from LOC 18 (folder 4 of 4), 1972 (Box-folder 31/6)
    Usarufas hold a funeral feast for Darlene Bee. Darlene Bee and Vida Chenoweth together. Papua New Guinea, Kaagu.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.1, 1971 (Box-folder 31/7)
    Music survey.
  - Photogrpahs from LOC 18.3a, 1968, 1986 (Box-folder 31/8)
    Photograph of Vida Chenoweth, 1968. Usarufa photograph, 1986.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.5, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 31/9)
    Darlene Bee and Vida Chenoweth. Kaarite village.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.8, 1965 (Box-folder 31/10)
    Vida Chenoweth with linguists.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.11, 1966 (Box-folder 31/11)
    Robert Young, Vida Chenoweth, and Rosemary Young. Translators for Bena Bena song. Papua New Guinea, Ukarumpa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.12, 1975, 1981, 1999 (Box-folder 31/12)
    Photographs, Siene and Kombra.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.15, LOC 18.16 (Box-folder 31/13)
    Ron Kendall recording Fore music.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.18, 1970 (Box-folder 31/14)
    Gimi spectacles. Papua New Guinea.
  - Photographs form LOC 18.19, 1966 (Box-folder 31/15)
    Kamano tribe members playing the famous "sacred flutes." Photograph of Vida Chenoweth and others. Territory of New Guinea.
  - Photographs form LOC 18.21, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 31/16)
    Eel on special decorated stick. Papua New Guinea, Eastern Highlands, Awa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.22, 1969 (Box-folder 31/17)
    Vida Chenoweth recording Kaarite men. Papua New Guinea, Eastern Highlands.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.24, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 31/18)
    Literacy, translation, and ethnomusicology at Ukarumpa headquarters. Papua New Guinea, Usarufa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.24a, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 31/19)
    Usarufa literacy and ethnomusicology at Kaagu village. Papua New Guinea, Usarufa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.25, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 31/20)
    Usarufa literacy and ethnomusicology at Kaarite village. Papua New Guinea, Usarufa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.25a, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 31/21)
    Vida Chenoweth, Darlene Bee, and Kaarite people and village. Papua New Guinea, Usarufa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.26, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 31/22)
    Usarufa travel and environs. Kaagu and Kaarite villages. Papua New Guinea, Usarufa.
  - Photographs from LOC 18.1981, 1981 (Box-folder 31/23)
    Vida Chenoweth, linguist. Papua New Guinea, Eastern Highlands Province, Kaarite village.
  - Photographs from LOC 19, 1992 (Box-folder 31/24)
    Snake dance at a pause. Photo by Dan Garst. Mota Island of Banks Islands, Vanuatu.
  - Photographs from LOC 20 (folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 31/25)
    Photographs from field research in Vanuatu, Tanna Island.
  - Photographs from LOC 20 (folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 31/26)
  - Photographs from LOC 20.1 (folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 31/27)
  - Photographs from LOC 20.1 (folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 31/28)